Hello friends, how are you all?  My name
is Arun and you are watching Finvst Pedia
YouTube channel.  Friends, in today's video
we are going to talk about a plan of ICIC PDL
whose name is
ICIC Pro Protect and Gain.  Now you must have
seen in the thumbnail that they are going to
discuss about the plan.
So if you are looking for a plan that
also provides you life insurance.   Along with this,
term insurance will also be provided
and then you will also get the returns related to the stock market.
That means,
if your money is invested in the stock market or
mutual fund, then
if you want the same kind of return that you can get from there, then this plan is a
very good plan, friends.  We will discuss this plan in
detail in this video.
I'll even show you the quotation.  I will
also show you how much
money you can get at what time.  So
if you watch the video till the end, all your
doubts will be cleared.  And I believe
that after this you will not need to watch any other video.
And obviously
friends, you can also contact us for the best deal.
You will
find our WhatsApp number in the description box.  So you can also chat with us
and we will try to get you the best deals
from ICICI Prudential.
So you
can also ask us any query and if you want to purchase this plan
then you can do it through us.
So you will get attractive offers
and some discounts there too, friends.
So now friends, let's talk generally about
what is this Pru Protect and Gain?
Generally, when you think about insurance,
two or three names come to your mind.  Like there is
life insurance, then there is term
insurance, health insurance is
a different category and then general insurance is a
different matter.  So generally, people who
want to have life insurance have taken it.
Then generally it is said
that brother, you are doing a job, if you take term insurance
also then you have to take term insurance also.  So in this
way you have many options.
And somewhere in today's
times, friends, it is important to
beat inflation.  So you want that insurance should
not just be your savings.  Your money may be
invested in such a market linked instrument where if I had invested in mutual funds,
I could have made a good amount of money.
So this is that plan, friends.  Now
what options do you get in this
?  Like generally we first check their website.
Then
I will tell you this quotation that I have made for you.
You will get to see some really cool things.
First of all,
friends, you will definitely get life insurance cover in this.
Life insurance cover
means that generally, if
something goes wrong with you, then the
nominee will definitely get some money.
Now those who buy term insurance, the
simple principle of term insurance is
that you are paying a premium
and if something goes wrong
during the policy period, then a
lump sum amount is given to your nominee.
So all those things are included in it.
What is additional to this?  You see, what
he has mentioned on the website is
portfolio strategies.  This means that
you have the option to decide
where to invest the money you are paying.
What type of portfolio should one have?   For
example, if you have seen, if you
know about the stock market, then your money is in many
places.  Like equity.   There are
specific things in equity also.
Like there are large cap funds or Nifty
, small cap, mid cap,
multi cap, then there are day funds,
multi asset allocation funds.  So you have the
choice to make any kind of
strategy as to
which type of stocks your money should be invested in.
No doubt you don't have to do this.   I
just need to tell you what kind of
portfolio I want.  Your fund
manager will do the rest.  You do
not need to decide whether you want to buy Reliance
or not.  You just have to tell whether you want to keep it
in large cap stocks or mid
cap, small cap or day
funds.  So these are all the things.
Apart from that, you can do this thing as many times as you want,
switch it for free.  Like right now you
feel like your money is going high in the market and
you feel that you have to
invest it in day funds, then invest it in day funds right now.
After a month if you feel that
brother I want to switch to equity then you can do it.
There is no charge for this.   There
is a free switch.  Apart from this,
systemic withdrawal friends.  Now SW plan
is fine for those who know.  Otherwise,
I will cover this as a separate topic
in our mutual fund series.  So you will
join the channel.  Please subscribe.  Keep
liking the video.
All the content related to the financial market will be available
here
and you will get the best.  It will be found that if you are
watching a video
then you will not need to watch anything related to it anywhere else.
And obviously friends, there is
tax benefit in all the insurance products
that
if you pay income tax under ATC, then
you can save it up to some limit.
So these are some of its benefits friends.
After that, the process to buy it easily has been
explained.  So
you can leave the process of buying from here.  If you
want, you can see it from here.  Otherwise
contact us.  You will get the best deals and
discounts there.  Whatever
query you have, try to understand one thing.
You can do this if you purchase this plan individually from ICICI's website.  There is no doubt in this.
But if you do it under us, then what
we have is that we have a tie up with Jel One.
We are authorized persons and Jel
One provides bulk policies to any company.  Be it
ICICI or HDFC.  So whenever there is a
matter of claim,
a person will be associated with you for the claim.  You will get a
lot of help in the claim.  Otherwise, if you
do it yourself, then to whom will you go to claim?   It's a
simple matter.  If we contact then
this document and that document, all this will continue.
So if you do it through us,
you are going to get a lot of benefits.
Obviously friends, you will get it at discounted rates
and you can also get attractive rewards.
So if you want, you
can also ask us through WhatsApp.  Otherwise you
can watch the video for more information.  There
is no problem.  Now
what is the boundary condition that how much minimum premium will have to be
paid?  Now, those who
want to purchase this plan.  First of all,
friends, your minimum premium should be ₹00
annually.  That means, if you talk about
someone thinking that I can
start with this for 2025,000 rupees, then it does not happen yearly,
friends.  Whatever private companies there are,
generally their ticket size is
higher.  Ticket size means your
annual premium will be at least
around Rs 400.  If
you are going for the life option, then I will tell you right now what life and growth are and what are the
differences between them.  If
you choose the growth option,
your minimum premium will be Rs 12,25,000.  Now
what is the difference between life and growth?  If I
tell you this right now, then you should
understand that if you choose your life option, then
your premium will be a
little higher for the same sum insured.  There will be
less growth but
your life and term covers will
reduce due to growth.  Now you might
not have understood how.  So let me explain
how.  For example, if we look at the life option, the
example he has explained.  Understand this first.
Then I am going to explain it to you in great detail.
Friends, the
video may be long but I would like to apologize for that
because it takes
some time to explain it properly.  Have some patience and
you will see that all your doubts will be cleared.
So as he has said that there is
a person named Animesh, he is 30 years old
and he purchases this plan
for the future of his family and he pays this policy
premium for 12 years.
That means there is an option in it.  You
can pay premium for 10 years.  You
can do 12 also.  So this is the option.
Suppose you pay premium till 12 and the
sum assured you choose is Rs 2 crore.
Now you will think that two crores is too much
sum assured?  Sum assured does
not mean friends that you will pay that much
money.  Sum Assured means
that if suppose something goes wrong
like in term insurance,
if you buy a term of Rs 1 crore, then the
premium you will be paying will be
around Rs 50600 per year.
If something goes wrong then
₹1 crore is given to your nominee.
Similarly, friends, the sum assured here is
₹ crore.  If something goes wrong
then ₹ crore will definitely be given to the nominee.
After that, they pay the premium for the premium paying term i.e. 12
years and the
policy will run for 40 years.  The policy will last for 40 years.
This means that you have to pay the premium only for 12
years.
You don't have to do anything in the remaining 28 years.  Then
your policy will continue.  So as you saw,
when he was 30 years old and he
paid this premium for 12 years, then for a
sum assured of Rs 2 crore, the premium is coming to
₹27838 per annum, that is, he will pay
₹7838 every year to ICICI Provincial for the next
12 years.  That means they will continue paying
this premium till they turn between 30 to 41 years of age.
Now what will you get in return for this
?  Now you have paid premium for 12 years.
Now how long will your policy last?  This policy will continue until
they turn 30 to 70 years old.
Now
what will happen in this duration?  That suppose
something goes wrong with them.
Suppose the premium was paid in the first year and
something went wrong in the second year itself.  So it is simple, the
life cover you are seeing is worth Rs 2
crore.  That means two crore rupees will definitely be
given to your nominee.
Friends, accidental death
cover is also included in this premium.  That is,
what is there in this premium is that if something goes wrong with you
then the life cover will become Rs 2 crore.
But if there is an accidental death, that is, if
you die in a road accident, then
you will get an additional Rs 2 crore
in accidental death cover.  That means this makes two to four
crores.  Now God forbid, it is
better that if nothing happens, we
assume that their policy continues and
if something happens during this period, then they will definitely
get this money.  It is a simple matter that
if nothing happens to 4 crores then what will happen to you
that this cover will continue till
70, that is even before 70, at the age of 69
if something wrong happens then also
they will get 4 crores but
if suppose it does not happen then what will happen till 70 years,
these benefits are continuing till 70th year,
if nothing happens then
what will they get,
friends generally you do not get anything in term insurance but
you will get it in this because this is a ULIP plan,
in this obviously your money invested will be
invested in the stock market i.e. there will be market
linked returns, so you see in this
they have written that @ 4% ARR, that
means if you get 4% interest
from the market then this money will become
691362, you will get this much money, if it grows at the rate of 8%
then this money will exceed 2 crores,
now think for yourself if you
know even a little bit about the stock market then
you will go and see the past returns yourself, however
past returns are future returns friends  There are
no guarantees, but if you look back into the past,
even if you have invested in Nifty 50
for 40 years,
you will see that the returns have never gone below 12%.
And if this 12%
goes away and we see it at 12% ARR, then its
value will become more than Rs 3.5 crore, friends.
If we get 15% then the value will be very high.
So friends, this is the benefit
of ULIP plan that it means
that your cover is also working well.  The
cover is running for Rs 2 crore.
However, many people may find the premium
high.  27838 So you
can take it for 1 crore also.  That means the
premium will be around Rs 1 lakh.  So the
calculation will be done accordingly.  I will do the same and
show you how your
premium will be and if nothing happens and
God's blessings remain, then it is a simple
matter that on maturity also you will get a good amount of
money which you are obviously earning by
investing in mutual funds or direct stocks, that
money will also become yours
and obviously the choice is also in your hands as to
which fund to invest the money in, i.e. whether to invest in
large cap, mid cap or
small cap, all this is
in your hands.  Whether you want to invest in dead funds or
liquid funds, everything is in your hands.
So friends, this plan that you just saw is
Life Option.  Now you have seen the life option.
Now let me explain growth with the
same example.  So if you come down a little,
now you can see what the bean is?  All other
conditions are same.  Look, he is only 30 years old.
Animesh is his name.  This policy is for 30 years
and the premium term is
also 40 years and the premium has to be paid for only 12
years.  Now look at the same,
if you look at the sum assured, then if you
choose the growth option, then
how much premium do you have to pay?  ₹1.5 lakh per
annum.  That means your premium has reduced slightly.
From there your premium reduced by Rs 50-55,000.
But the growth option means
that your money will keep getting invested again and again.
The money you are making will be
reinvested every year.
Whatever interest is earned in one year will be directly
invested again in the next year.   It will be
invested there in those same funds.
So see what is happening in this?  Your
premium also reduces by ₹1.5 lakh.  But
if you look at the life cover and accidental death cover here, they will be reduced.  There
we were getting this Rs. crore in the life option.
Now look here,
your life cover is approximately ₹54 lakh.  Accidental death
cover is Rs 54 lakh.  And there is one more thing I forgot to
mention.  There is also accidental disability cover.  It was there
above and it is there in this also.  What this means is that
by chance, suppose he met with an
accident and it happened
in such a condition that there was some problem with his hands and legs
that he would not be able to earn further, that is, he would become
disabled.  Even then you will be
given this cover.  In the above case, the
life insurance cover will be given Rs 2 crore
and here it will be given Rs 54 lakh.  Now see,
despite the premium being low, if you
see that the money is invested in the growth option, then
if nothing happens for 70 years, then at the
rate of 4% ARR, you will
get Rs 3432000, at the rate of 8% you will get Rs 1 crore 47 lakh and at the rate of
12%, then it will
reach around Rs 2.5 crore. Even if you see,
returns fluctuate in the market, so
obviously this money will be at the
rate of whatever percentage is there at that time, but still you should
assume that if the past returns are repeated, then at
least if you remain
invested in Nifty 50, you should
easily get 12%, so this money will
easily become Rs 2.5-3 crore.  Now
you have all those options in it which include the
option of systematic withdrawal and SWP.  You
also have the option of taking part payment.  You will find all these options here which are
almost available in mutual funds.
So,
broadly speaking, you have understood here
what changes take place in life and growth.
Friends, if you like the video till now then please
like it.  Please subscribe to the channel
as you will find less such content
here but whatever
video you get will be such that you will
not need to look for it anywhere else.  And obviously
friends, if you want all these plans, be it health
insurance, life insurance, term insurance
, mutual fund, stock market,
demat, anything, financial product, then
you
can also contact us in One Basket.   You will
find the WhatsApp number in the description,
chat on it and then according to your need,
friends, someone from our team will
talk to you and will
guide you in the best way.  You will
also get rewards at discounted rates, so you will get all that.
So friends, this generally became a plan.
Now let me tell you a case by
making a premium quotation that if suppose there
is a 30 year old person and if he was planning to
buy a term insurance of Rs. 1 crore as premium, then in
lieu of that if he
wants to buy this plan i.e. wants to
buy a ULIP plan of ICIC Prudential &
Protect then what will be the plan,
for that I will show you the quotation
and show you everything in it that when will you
get how much money, what will happen, how to do
things, so let us move on to that now, so
now friends, see, now I have
made a plan for you in which the
person is 30 years old and for him,
instead of term insurance of Rs. 1 crore, we will
talk about ICIC Protect & Protect plan. So see, I have
already made the quotation.  Age is 30.
Gender is a combination of these.  Now suppose he was
thinking of taking a term insurance of Rs 1 crore.
Then he decided that I will
look at the ULIP plan and this plan
of ICICI seems good to me.  So now
look at this plan, for how many
years have they made it, I had told there for 40 years.
Now here we talk about 30 years
and obviously friends, if we make it
40 years for Rs 1 crore then the
premium will reduce a little more because you
can understand that in that case your
time duration is increasing more, so your
premium will reduce a little bit.
So if we continue this for 30 years,
suppose
June has started from May 2025, when we talk about it at
any time, you can understand
that suppose I purchased the plan in May 2025, then
your annual premium is
coming to
₹12919, so you have to pay this
₹12919 throughout the year, let me
tell you one more thing that it is not that you have to pay
it only once, if
you feel that you have the money all at once then do it,
that is the best option
because there you save some money, you
can divide it monthly also
but the premium will increase a little
because there you will pay a little every month at the
time of installment, you can understand it like EMI.
You can also get it divided monthly.
But a little bit of premium will
increase there.  If you want to save some premium from there, then pay
₹12,919 yearly.  Now imagine that you have to pay this for 10 years.  That
means it will be paid from May 2025 to May 2034.
₹12,919 every year.  Now what will he get in return for the
premium he was paying
?  Firstly, you
can see in this entire line that this policy will continue from May 2025 to
May 2055 i.e. for the next 30 years.
You have to pay
premium for only 10 years.  Now in that case
that we were talking about earlier, we were
talking about it for 12 years.  Now here we have made it
10 years and the policy term is
how many years should the policy last?  For 30 years.
What will you get now?  In this,
see what benefits you will
get?  Now if we talk about it, then here first of all
you need protection.  Now
what does protection mean?  Will go.
Generally, whatever insurance you see that is sold,
why do you want to purchase insurance
?  Because brother, your life should be
protected.  Like first of all life
insurance cover so that if something goes wrong
then what will my nominee get that he will get
some money if something happens to me.
So how much is the life insurance cover
?  Worth one crore.  That means if something wrong happens
then instantly you will get ₹1
crore and whichever nominee you make, be it your wife,
father, mother or your children, they will get ₹1
crore.  How long
should the misshapening last?  That is, if suppose you
purchased this policy in May 2025 or in whichever month, you paid the premium and the
policy document came to you, if
God forbid, if this happens a few days after that, then
also if this policy exists, then
he will get ₹1 crore, if something like this happens till May 2025, then ₹
1 crore of life
insurance, if this premium that you
saw includes accidental death cover, then
if suppose there is an accidental death, then
you will get ₹1 crore of life insurance, along with this, the nominee will also get ₹1 crore of accidental death cover,
so the total becomes ₹2 crore
and you can see
what is its duration, you are covered from May 2025 to May 2025,
apart from that, suppose what
I was talking about disability in Accendal,
if some disability occurs, then also ₹1
crore will be given here, that is, from May 2025 to
May  Even if such disability occurs till 205,
₹1 crore will be given.
So friends, you can understand that for those who were going to
buy life insurance or term insurance, the
solution has been found here that
brother, this is what happens in term insurance.  Apart
from this, there is no maturity benefit
there.  So here this
term insurance cover is done.  Life
insurance cover is done.  Now the question comes to wealth
creation,
how will I make more money at the same time?
Brother, if nothing happens to me, it is not that
my
premium will be lost for the money I have given to the insurance company.  What should I get in exchange for him
?  So now you will get
this wealth creation, friends, see you have
purchased a policy for 30 years, then when May 2055
comes, that is, when 30 years will be completed, then you will be
given lump sum maturity benefit, that is,
what is the lump sum maturity benefit, that the
money which will be received by investing in the market,
you will get that much money at that time, for example, if your return is
8%, let's say the same, we discussed it a while
ago, then
you will get approximately ₹3298258 at the rate of 8%,
obviously I have already talked about a while ago
that if you see the returns in Nifty anywhere in the past,
even from 2008 to 2020, when there was a
recession in 2008, the market saw the fall of Covid in 2020,
so even in that period,
if we talk about it, even in that period, there have been
returns of more than 12%, friends, so if it happens like that,
more than 12, then approximately this Rs
1 crore  It will be more than that. Now think about
how much you had invested, if you
look at it that way, you will see that you are giving ₹12919 approximately
₹13000 for 10 years, so approximately how much will it be,
10 lakhs and 3000 * 10 and 3000
that is approximately, you can assume that you will
invest ₹1300.  What are you getting by investing ₹1300
?  Life insurance of Rs 1 crore includes
your accidental
death benefit of Rs 1 crore and even disability benefit.
So, both your term and
life are covered in this for Rs 1 crore each.  And what you have done is
approximately Rs 10 lakh 300.  After that,
if it grows at the rate of 12% after 30 years, you will
get a lump sum benefit of more than Rs 1 crore.  Even if
nothing happens, then remove this Rs 1 crore.
Then, the maturity
benefit of more than Rs 1 crore can also be availed at the rate of 12%. If the
rate remains at 8%, then this much
money will be available and 4%. However,
think for yourself in 30 years. The stock
market will generate returns at some places.
Although it may not seem realistic, but
you always understand that the company
operates a little safely. So, this is written here so that
you do not get worried and
you do not feel that very high returns have been shown.
But it is possible that if, suppose
someone is a big risk taker, if he
invests
his money in a small cap fund for 30 years, then in the past
you will see that even 25-30% returns have been received.
If that happens, then the value of this money will
increase a lot. So,
friends, this is a benefit.
This plan is more suitable for those who
want life cover and are thinking of buying term insurance,
like many salaried
employees.  If they have a good salary, they do
take term insurance, but
according to me, instead of term, this thing is such that
in this you also have market linked
returns and your money is also
invested in the market.  You
can also understand from the mutual fund form that you are
invested in the mutual fund.  Because if you
buy only term, then in some policies it happens
that your premium
is returned.  But just think about it,
what happens in it is that
if you are taking a 40 year term plan, then
you will have to pay the entire premium only for 40 years
or some time duration is
given in it that okay, make it till 30 years.
So even if I get that back, I will
not get any benefit.  In
a way, that money became zero for me.
So if I am investing and
some company is keeping my money somewhere, then
I should also get returns on it.  So
friends, this plan is the best.  If I
look at your ULIP plan, if you
want to invest in the market
and also want to buy live and terminal at the same time, then
this plan seems best for you.
Friends, if you like the video till now then
keep liking and subscribing.
I will talk to you further and
I will tell you everything here.  Now see, in this, if
we choose this life option
in the growth option, then
no doubt your premium will reduce a bit in the growth option.
But then obviously the live and
death covers here will reduce for you.  Now if
you want this plan for yourself then
obviously contact us.  We will
prepare a quotation as per your requirement and share it with you and if you
find it suitable then you can also purchase through us.  The
entire ICIC team will help you with our
help.  It is not that we are getting the
plan purchased separately and giving it to you.  We have a
tie up with ICICI.  Friends,
if you look at all the companies, be it ICICI, HDFC, Tata
AI, any of them, if you
want any of them, we can provide you the quotation.
Otherwise, if you want,
we can also provide this at a discounted rate.
So now let me talk in some more detail about the
premium, it is important for you to know
what is there in this premium?  So you can see this is your average
premium every year.  This 12919 is for 10 years,
remember GST is not included in it.
So if we include 4.5% GST then
it will be fine there.  After that,
if we talk about the detailed breakup of
what all you are taking in this premium, then
see, your base premium was ₹80,000.
Now what does base premium
mean?  The accidental depth benefit that you
saw was of ₹1 crore and the
accidental disability benefit of ₹1
crore, if you do not want it separately, you
can remove it from this.  This
is the rider premium for which you are
paying ₹22,919 annually
for accidental insurance of Rs 1 crore or for
accidental disability.  So if you do
n't want this then you can remove it from here, then
only ₹80,000 plus the applicable
tax will be charged there.  So the
thing to see here is that if you
want this then this is your premium breakup.
Now why should ICICI choose?  Well, this is
not a sponsored video, friends,
but obviously you can read this in these quotations.
Claim settlement etc., well
you don't have to worry about it even if you are getting it done
through us because
you will need a whole team.  You will
get full support.  Right from the start, when
you complete the policy, a relationship
manager will be appointed to you.  The one that
will help you friends is tax saving.
Now look, if we talk in detail, then look,
you can see some more things in it.
When the quotation is made, you will
see here that one thing
is written here that fund opted for, what does it mean that
when I got this quotation made, I said
that where should my money be invested in the stock market,
so see,
I have invested 75% in multicap growth fund
and 25% in income fund, if you want,
you have the option for this, even when your app is made, you can do it through that also, whether
you want to
invest in small cap, Nifty, day
funds, if you do not want to take risk, then you can invest
in liquid funds also, but the
returns there will be negligible, so
if you see, if you are investing somewhere for 30-40 years, then I
believe that if you are not 30 years old, then you should
invest more in equity, at
least 75%, the remaining 25% you
can invest in day funds, you can invest in balance funds, that is
your choice.  You can see
that all these things are written
here.  When you get the policy done,
all the details will be asked from you.   Whether you are a
smoker or not.  If you are a smoker then obviously the
premium
increases because your chances of getting sick and maybe even
death increase.   There are
some major diseases like cancer etc., so
for smokers or non-smokers, whenever you get
any insurance, be it
health, life or term, then
give all the correct information there, only then you will
not face any problem in getting the claim.  There is complete
assurance that if you tell everything correctly
and the work is done honestly, it will always be
good.  Now you can see in the premium summary what all
things are there and how much tax is
levied on what.  These are all the things which are total now
you can see them here.  After that, if we
look at it, then this benefit illustration has been
discussed.  So let me
explain it to you.  You will understand what he wants to
say.  Ok?  Ok?  So let's go
down a little and I will explain to you a table
that what does all this written
mean?  So let's go up
and as you can see, your
policy year is given from the time you
start, next if this
was a policy for 30 years, then
this year from 1st to 30th would have been given.  Look, it's only till 30.
So this first column is for 30 years,
what will happen in the first year?  If something happens,
your premium is gone.  For example, let us assume that in the
first year your
base premium is Rs 80,000.  After that, the
8000 rupees that are going to be spent in 80 years,
now you do not need to see all this, what is
this, what is the mobility charge,
what are the other charges, the company has
told you that most of the
charges of mobility are 10675 according to the death rate of mobility,
you do not need to see all these things, but
suppose, if
God forbid something happens to you in this duration, then
what will you get, that is more important for you to know, so for example,
if suppose in the first
year someone paid a premium of ₹80 and
obviously, God forbid, he dies in the same year.
So you can see the death
benefit.  Now there is this strange term in this,
friends, death benefit, meaning the benefit of dying.
But now this is the language of insurance.
We cannot do anything about it.
So if someone pays a premium of Rs 80,000
and dies in the same year.
So you can see that your nominee will get Rs 1 crore in the
same year.  It is
not that if you reach the first year then you will get it after two-three
years.  It's not like that.  You will get it at the same time.
After that, friends, you
can see the fund value at the end of the year.  Now it is
not the case that if death benefit is given then the fund
value will not be available.  For example, if you
need money in the same year, then see, it is written above that it is
4% gross investment, this is calculated at 4%,
here it is calculated at 8%, so the
actual fund value
depends on the market.  If at the same time,
suppose you got 1215% in one year, then you will
get it accordingly.  So if you see it at 4% then it will be
63345 and after that if you
see it here at the rate of 8% then if you see the fund value at the end
of the year then it will be 6670. Now you must be thinking
that I paid 80000 and
how did the fund value at the end of the year become 63000 at 4%,
this has reduced because of this, the
company must
keep some amount to earn, so it
removed it from here, now as the time passes
this value will keep increasing, it is not that
it will remain less every time, now if you look ahead and
see the first year, I have told you, you must have understood,
similarly if you see it at the rate of 8% then the
fund value and death benefit are obviously
this, all this is written here.  Now
if you go down, I am saying approximately
after 26 years, let us see
what will happen after the policy has been in operation for 26 years,
you will have to pay some premium for 26 years, now
see for how long you will have to pay the premium, obviously
in the starting 10 years, after that all the
premiums will be zero, it is 80000 till the 10th year,
after that everything is zero here, so
if you think that you
completed the policy for 10 years and in the 11th year,
suppose something happens, some such problem occurs, then
you can see that you will definitely get Rs 1 crore, that is, you will definitely get the
death
benefit and obviously the
fund value.  If you look at it at 8% then it will be
₹915,000, still you will say that
friend, if you do my approximately ₹8,000 * 10 then approximately
₹8 lakh has been invested.  At the rate of 8%,
you got interest of around ₹9,15,000.  Now
as time passes, you already know the concept of mutual funds
that compound interest
is available in it.  So suppose that
in your 29 years, if you either need money
or God forbid, some death wave occurs.
Or suppose the policy is in its 30th year,
meaning you got it done in 30 years
when you are 60 years old.  If there is some mortality at that time,
i.e. death occurs, then
one crore rupees will definitely be received.  If you have
taken the accidental rider then you will
get Rs 1 crore.  So the total will be Rs 2 crore.
Also, if
nothing happens for 8% in 30 years,
how much money should you get?  So
how much did you invest
in starting?  ₹0000 * 10 means a total of
₹8 lakh was invested.  Because
rider calculation is not included in it.  So
₹8 lakh was invested.  And if you
look after 30 years, then at the rate of 8% it itself is telling
that you will get Rs
32,98,258.  Now, if you
want, you can check this by entering it in any calculator
that if you get 12 or 15% return, then
this money will become more than Rs 1.25 crore.
So this
is a market dependent return.  Therefore, the
calculation of 4% and 8% is shown here clearly.
But you know about the past,
as I already told you,
go and check the past returns.  You can withdraw it on any mutual fund
website or wherever you like, at
any time frame.  If it is for
this duration, then whether it is Nifty or any other
instrument, it has given a return of more than 12%.
So I
hope friends, you must have understood this table also.
After that,
you do not need to see all these things in your quotation.  All this is the
company's own charge, what is the
total,
they have told in detail that brother,
what is ours in it, what are the things, what are the things.
Apart from this, friends, you will also get all those options
as to what you
want to invest this money in, that is,
I have already told you the money you are investing.   You have to
invest in large cap, mid cap
, small cap.  So
friends, all those things
remain there like the same.  You will have the option there.
Obviously, once you take the policy, you will
get the ICICI app.  You can go there and see all these
things in detail.  So I hope
friends, I have covered this plan of ICICI Prudential,
Protect and Growth
Again very well.
If you still have any doubt then
you can write it in the comment.  I will
answer that.  Otherwise, this is the best option
you have.  If CSO needs information about purchasing this, then you will
find our WhatsApp number in the description.  You can
contact us on that.
We will try to provide the best that we can for you.
Rest, when you contact us,
we will tell you all the details and whatever you might be missing.  So I
hope friends, the video might have been a bit long
but I might have been able to give you a lot in it.
So if you liked the video then do
like it.
Do subscribe to the channel and
for such information, friends,
subscribe to the channel for other different plans.  Till then take
good care of yourselves friends.
Thank you so much friends.